A Guide to the Nathaniel Francis Cabell Papers, 1722-1879
Library of Virginia
- Letters, 19 November, 29 December 1860, 22 March 1861, Edmund Taylor, [Campbell County], to Nathaniel Francis Cabell, [Nelson County] regarding modifications in his Agricola essay., 14 p. (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Letters, 10, 21, 31 March, 4 April, 26 June, 15, 17 July 1879, Nathaniel Francis Cabell, [Nelson County], to Colonel W. C. Knight on the history of agriculture in Virginia., 25 p. (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Bibliography, n.d., or Sources of a history of agriculture in Virginia., 3 leaves and 36 p.. (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Classified index, n.d., to articles in Skinner's American Farmer., 1 leaf and 3 p. (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Index, n.d., to authors of anonymous articles in Farmers Register., 8 p. (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Index, n.d., to matters treated in the Westover Manuscripts., 3 p. (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Some fragments, n.d., from an intended report on a post-revolutionary history of agriculture in Virginia., 24 p. (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Rules, n.d., for judging a horse's age., 4 p. (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Rules, n.d., for observance on the Bremo plantations and memoranda for practical agricultors, including advice on slaves, by John H. Cocke, [Fluvanna County]., 7 p. (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Extracts, n.d., from treatise on silk manufacture in Lardner's Cyclopedia, and information on tobacco from Harris' Voyages., 4 p. (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Lists, June 1879, of papers from the collection of Joseph C. Cabell, of papers from the collection of General John H. Cocke, and of papers on matters of agriculture by General John H. Cocke., 3 leaves. (Box 1, Folder 74)